{
  "analysis": {
    "folgen": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1, 
          "frage": "TestfrageFolgen", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortFolgen!"
        },
        {
          "id": 2, 
          "frage": "TestfrageFolgen2", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortFolgen2!"
        }
      ]
    },
    "reihen": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1, 
          "frage": "TestfrageReihen", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortReihen!"
        },
        {
          "id": 2, 
          "frage": "TestfrageReihen2", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortReihen2!"
        }
      ]
    },
    "differenzialrechnung": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1, 
          "frage": "TestfrageDiff", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortDiff!"
        },
        {
          "id": 2, 
          "frage": "TestfrageDiff2", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortDiff2!"
        }
      ]
    },
    "integralrechnung": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1, 
          "frage": "TestfrageInteg", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortInteg!"
        },
        {
          "id": 2, 
          "frage": "TestfrageInteg2", 
          "antwort": "TestantwortInteg2!"
        }
      ]
    }
  },
  "theoretischeInformatikI": {
    "algebraischeStrukturen": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "frage": "testfrageTheo",
          "antwort": "testantwortTheo"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "frage": "testfrageTheo2",
          "antwort": "testantwortTheo2"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "frage": "testfrageTheo3",
          "antwort": "testantwortTheo3"
        }
      ]
    },
    "logik": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "frage": "testfrageLogik",
          "antwort": "testantwortLogik"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "frage": "testfrageLogik2",
          "antwort": "testantwortLogik2"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "frage": "testfrageLogik3",
          "antwort": "testantwortLogik3"
        }
      ]
    },
    "algorithmen": {
      "fragenUndAntworten": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "frage": "testfrageAlgo",
          "antwort": "testantwortAlgo"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "frage": "testfrageAlgo2",
          "antwort": "testantwortAlgo2"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "frage": "testfrageAlgo3",
          "antwort": "testantwortAlgo3"
        }
      ]
    }
  }
}